{
    "subject": "Mieszko_III_the_Old",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Elisabeth_of_Hungary__1128\u20131154_",
    "human_readable": "Mieszko III the Old is married to Elisabeth of Hungary (1128\u20131154).",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9872767329216003,
            "question": "When was Elisabeth of Hungary married to Mieszko III the Old?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9566424489021301,
            "question": "What was the relationship between Mieszko III the Old and Elisabeth of Hungary?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9398325681686401,
            "question": "To whom was Mieszko III the Old married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9246790409088135,
            "question": "Who was married to Elisabeth of Hungary?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8543336987495422,
            "question": "Who is Mieszko III the Old?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8216737508773804,
            "question": "What is the name of Elisabeth of Hungary's husband?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6622616052627563,
            "question": "Was Mieszko III the Old a king?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6370680928230286,
            "question": "What was Elisabeth of Hungary known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5358554720878601,
            "question": "Where did Elisabeth of Hungary come from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49298691749572754,
            "question": "What years did Elisabeth of Hungary live?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Mieszko III the Old is married to Elisabeth of Hungary (1128\u20131154).",
            "html": "yago_29331_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where did Elisabeth of Hungary come from?",
            "html": "yago_29331_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What was Elisabeth of Hungary known for?",
            "html": "yago_29331_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Was Mieszko III the Old a king?",
            "html": "yago_29331_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29331_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29331_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29331_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29331_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29331_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29331_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29331_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29331_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29331_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29331_79.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents provide information about Mieszko III and his wife Elisabeth of Hungary, including their marriage date in 1135. This supports the statement that Mieszko III the Old is married to Elisabeth of Hungary (1129-1155), with slight discrepancies in birth year details but consistent overall."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}